## **CURRICULUM VITAE**

# Mg Aung Myo Swe

Software Engineer

Hlaing Township, Yangon

aungmyoswe.dev@gmail.com, 09798722263, 09961099137

https://www.linkedin.com/in/aung-myo-swe/

https://aungmyoswe.info



#### **Personal Profile**

Experienced web developer with a strong background in developing web applications for the Odoo ERP Companies. 5+ years of industry experience includes programming, debugging, and wireframes. Motivated junior web developer looking for a role as full-stack web developer at Software Development Industries. Passionate about building first-class web applications. Developed an e-commerce website and integrate for Ecommerce Mart with Odoo ERP. Relevant skills include DNS Management, Database, Debugging, Installation, Configuration and more.

### **Education Background**

- Graduated B.C.Sc (2013/2014)
- ➤ Web Technology with PHP (IMCEITS)

### **Experience**

Infinite Business Solution (Jan - 2018 to Feb - 2019)
 Mayankone Township, Yangon

Junior Develop & Web Developer

- Develop and design new module and customize module of Odoo HR, POS, inventory, sale & purchase and hotel management system.
- Migrate data & code as per the requirements
- Wrote backend python programming and frontend JS, CSS, SCSS, XML
- Bug fixing, performance, optimization and production support
- Gathering all requirements and developing & customization the modules accordingly.

- Installing & configuration of the Odoo server and ubuntu & window OS
- Developed by Odoo version (7, 8, 10, 11, 12)
- Zando Technologies (July 2019 to Dec 2021)
  Hlaing Township, Yangon

#### Web Developer

- Develop and design new module and customize module of Odoo Sale & Purchase, Invoicing and Mall Management System.
- Migrate data & code as per the requirements
- Integrate with third party application.
- Wrote backend python programming and frontend JS, CSS, SCSS, XML
- Bug fixing, performance and optimization.
- Deployment GitHub and Odoo.sh CD, CI tool
- Developed by Odoo version (13, 14)
- Bagan Innovation Technologies (Feb 2022 to Dec 2022)
  Hlaing Township, Yangon

#### Senior Web Developer

- Develop and design new module and customize module of Odoo ERP & Ecommerce.
- Migrate data & code as per the requirements
- Integrate with third party application.
- Wrote backend python programming & PHP and frontend JS, CSS, SCSS, XML
- Bug fixing, performance and optimization.
- Deployment GitHub and Odoo.sh CD, CI tool
- Installing & configuration of the Odoo server and ubuntu & window OS
- Ectivise Solutions (Feb 2023 to August 2023)
  Singapore

#### Software Engineer (Remote-contract)

- Build scripts to automate complex network configuration.
- Python programming language for software-defined networking and migrate data & code as per the requirements
- Integrate with third party application.

- Wrote backend python programming & NodeJS and frontend ReactJS, CSS, Tailwind CSS, Bootstrap
- Bug fixing, performance and optimization.
- Deployment GitHub, Docker, ESXI
- Installing and configuration of the server and ubuntu & window OS

#### Skills

Web Technologies: HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, JQuery, TypeScript, Ajax, JSON, XML,

Bootstrap, Tailwind CSS

Web Framwork : Odoo, Django, Laraval, Express.js, React[S

Programming: Python(Advanced), PHP(Advance), C++(Intermidate), Java(Intermidate)

Database : PostgreSQL, MySQL, MongoDB, SQL

#### Other

Cloud : AWS Cloud Server (EC2, Lightsail), ESXi (VMWare), Odoo.sh

Server : Ubuntu(linux), Window(OS)

Project: HRMS, HMS, Sale, Purchase, Invoice & Inventory Management System,

Netowrk Monitoring System(Automation), Ecommerce, POS System

## **Expected Salary**

> 5000 SGD (Negotiate)